Today I'd like to talk about the theory of 3s.
Whenever you're working with beads, wires, or whatever type of necklace, bracelet, or earrings.
Threes are really the best way to kind of correspond your jewelry.
You'll see right here is a necklace.
We go 1, 2, 3 beads.
Usually 2 small on the side and one large in the middle.
That's usually a very typical thing that you'll see in hoops or even regular earrings.
We have 2 small and one large earring.
For necklaces, you'll see this particular necklace starts off with a large pendant and then you have 3 jade beads with connectors, and you have 3 diamond shapes as well.
It really corresponds and makes the jewelry, or the art behind the jewelry really connect and come together.
As you're deciding what beads are going to go with what, you may want to think about the theory of 3.